In the end, I didn't
really do anything at all.
I wonder if they'll be mad.
(wall rumbling)
(wall exploding)
Ah.
You on the other hand, though,
you really worked way too hard.
Awe.
(gasps)
(chuckles) Oh, you poor thing.
(eerie music)
Shall I put you
out of your misery?
Hold on now.
Don't go acting on
your own, human,
or you'll die.
Oh, stop, I was just being kind,
which a curse might
not quite understand.
(eerie music continues)
So, got the goods?
(chuckles) Without a hitch.
All six of the special-grade
Sukuna's Finger cursed objects
that Jujutsu High possessed,
and the other
special-grade cursed object,
Cursed Wombs Death
Paintings, One through Three.
[Suguru] Most of the
temples at Jujutsu High
are actually just a facade.
Tengen's barrier keeps their
positions changing every day.
And within those, only one
of over a thousand doors
actually leads to the storeroom
that holds cursed objects
as dangerous as the fingers.
Each day, only Tengen knows
which door leads to
the true storehouse,
so I doubt anyone
will interfere.
Who's this Tengen
you're talking about?
A sorcerer with
immortality technique.
Ah! He must be even
stronger than Gojo!
Immortality, but
not eternal youth.
You can think of him
as sort of just a tree.
Tengen basically doesn't
interfere with the world,
aside from maintaining barriers,
so you really don't
have to worry about him.
Remember the finger we
let Jujutsu High retrieve?
I put a charm comprised of
Mahito's cursed energy on it
before they collected it.
It's under a single-layer seal,
so they won't
bother to remove it.
He'll be able to find it easily.
And are there gatekeepers?
Tengen does keep two attendants
between the door
and the storeroom.
Both chumps.
More importantly, before
the veil actually goes down,
I'd like you to very quietly
thin out the sorcerers
stationed at the school
to lighten the burden on Hanami.
Mm-hmm.
[Hanami] Why not
just seal Satoru Gojo
inside the veil while
we have the chance?
[Suguru] Because we don't
want to draw his attention
toward Mahito's main mission.
And we need him to
exercise his full power,
or it won't be a
proper test of the veil.
Trapping the students
inside will be more effective.
[Hanami] Is it okay to
kill all but Sukuna's vessel?
[Suguru] That's fine, but
I wouldn't recommend it.
[Hanami] Hmm?
[Suguru] So far,
Sukuna's actions
have not been quite
what I expected.
This is just my
guess, but I believe
one of the other students acts
as kind of a land
mine for Sukuna.
Worst case scenario,
if we step on that,
all of our current
plans will be ruined.
Then why don't we just go
and kidnap Itadori
ahead of time?
We'll be using him as a pawn.
But Itadori, or rather
Sukuna himself,
is also a type of
land mine for us.
That applies to both
us and Jujutsu High.
We shouldn't agitate it until
the moment we want more chaos:
October 31st in Shibuya.
Everything we can
use to seal Satoru Gojo
we should keep in
reserve until then.
We'll have a few curse
users accompany us, too.
But Juzo Kumiya,
he's disposable.
He's not the kind of person
who can follow a plan
all the way through.
He'll just get in our way later.
And we'll have a different
human as a monitor
for our test run of the
veil, so get along with them.
Yeah, you hear that,
Jogo? So get going.
(grunts) I'm not going, anyway.
Come on, Hanami, wake up.
Let's go.
[Hanami] Mahito?
Hm?
[Hanami] Trying to pump
the brakes on my hostility
is incredibly stressful.
You're sounding more like
a curse every day, Hanami.
(opening theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
(birds chirping)
Next up are the casualties.
Three second-grade sorcerers,
one semi-first-grade sorcerer,
five supervisors,
and two guards.
They were all on
standby at the school
and all of them were
there working separately
from Gojo and Principal Yaga.
We're still waiting on
the report from Ieiri,
but we're nearly
certain it was the work
of the same cursed spirit that
Nanami encountered before.
(Satoru grunts)
What do you think?
Should we share this
information with the students
and the other sorcerers?
No.
It's probably better to
keep this among ourselves.
We don't want to give
curse users certainty
that special-grade
objects were stolen.
Has our captured
curse user spilled?
(sighs) Well, it's no
problem getting him to talk.
But what he says? It's all
just irrelevant nonsense.
Although, it's interesting
that he's claiming
he was only in the attack
because he was ordered to
come as part of a certain deal.
I just wanted to make
myself a coat rack.
The monk promised me that.
I don't know his name.
In fact, I don't even know
if it was a man or a woman.
Just a brat with
white hair in a bob cut.
A mysterious androgynous
monk kid with a bob haircut.
Ring any bells?
Nah. The guy sounds
like a bullshitter.
Have we got anyone
skilled at confessions?
How did these outsiders
and a cursed spirit
get through all of
Tengen's barriers?
[Satoru] That was
probably the work
of the special-grade
cursed spirit
the students were fighting.
That one has a unique presence.
Even though it's
a cursed spirit,
it's incredibly close
to a natural spirit.
According to Aoi, it was
able to hide among plants,
and Tengen's barrier doesn't
function against plants.
Remember, Tengen's
barrier puts all its power
into hiding, not protecting,
so once you get
in, it's kind of weak.
Are they worried
about Sukuna's fingers
enhancing Yuji's potential?
Or are they trying to
enhance themselves?
Something isn't sitting right.
Well, for the time being,
at least our
students are all safe.
(Gakuganji grunts)
But obviously the exchange
event will have to be canceled.
Hold on! Since when is that
a decision we get to make?
[Group] Huh?
So how's it possible
that you get along
with a gorilla like Todo?
Well, the two of us got along,
but it was like, I mean, I
do remember everything,
but it feels like I wasn't
exactly myself at the time.
What do you mean?
Were you drinking?
You seriously believe I
could've been drinking liquor
in a situation like that?
That woulda been insane.
Anyway, I'm just
glad your injuries
weren't too serious, Fushiguro.
To your health and this pizza.
[Fushiguro] You could've
brought me something
easier to digest.
No complaining.
Apparently, I got off easier
because my cursed
energy was all gone,
and Ieiri was still
able to fix me up
as soon as the
roots were removed.
[Itadori] Huh, so
that's what happened?
[Kugisaki] You should know.
You fought against
them too, didn't you?
Itadori.
Huh?
[Fushiguro] You know,
you've grown a lot stronger.
Hm?
Before,
we both said that we
stood by our convictions.
I still think that's true.
But then on the other hand,
one could say that we're
both wrong about all of that.
Huh?
Some questions don't
have any answers.
Don't think so
hard. You'll go bald.
You're right,
there is no answer.
I know it's just a matter
of trying to accept it.
But why accept
something you don't want?
Only weak sorcerers do that.
So I've decided
I'll surpass you.
(laughs) You never change.
Did I get left out of
the conversation again?
There ya go. That's my
brother and his friends for ya.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Wait, where are
you going, Brother?
Hey, hold up!
Look, I'm grateful to you,
but come on, give me a break!
You know damn well
that I wasn't thinking
straight back then!
[Todo] What are you saying?
We've been so close ever
since middle school, Brother!
[Itadori] Since middle school?
I didn't go to your
middle school!
[Miwa] Hello! Useless Miwa here.
And even though I
call myself useless,
I don't actually think
that I'm all that bad.
But it is true that
while everyone else
was risking their lives fighting
during the special-grade
cursed spirit's attack,
I was fast asleep.
And now I feel ashamed.
Also, I wonder who
broke my sword?
Was it Mai's older sister?
After all of that,
we thought the exchange
event would be canceled,
but now, after taking a
day off, here we all are.
[Satoru] Play ball!
[Miwa] Playing baseball!
(upbeat theme music)
(casual theme music)
(birds chirping)
So anyway, that happened
and some people died.
But what now?
Keep going?
Uh, I have no idea
what to say to that.
Get real.
Huh?
[Todo] The Exchange Event
will continue, of course!
[Itadori] Todo!
What are your reasons?
For one, only those who
have a direct connection
to the victims have any
right to mourn them.
It would be rude of
us to butt in there.
And secondly, if
people have died,
that's all the
more reason for us
to work to become stronger.
Acquired strength can only come
from the
accumulation of results.
Tasting defeat and
savoring victory,
these are the things
that lead us to grow!
The most important thing now
is for those results
to continue to exist.
This is surprising. Todo
sounds almost reasonable.
Reasonably crazy.
Third, when a student feels like
they weren't able to
bring out their best,
it'll hang over
them until they die.
[Satoru] How old are you?
Yeah, I'm fine with all that.
We'll still win anyway.
He does have a point there.
Kamo, shouldn't you be resting?
I'm in.
[Inumaki] Salmon.
How do we pair up
for the individual fights?
Huh? There are no
individual battles.
The Exchange Event always has
the principals of
the two schools.
Each propose a form of
competition for the two days,
or that's how it's
supposed to be.
Every year 'til now, the first
day has been team battles
and the second
individual battles.
[Inumaki] Salmon.
(all grumbling)
I don't like routines
but this is how it's done.
Every year we put the
competition methods here
and pull one out.
Huh?
Principal Gakuganji's
previous visit was to discuss
what items might be needed
on the day of the event.
[Itadori] Huh? What?
-Huh?
-Whoa!
Baseball?
You too?
[Gakuganji] What's
going on here, Yaga?
[Yaga] I don't know!
I was sure I put
individual battles in there.
Hey! Get back here, Satoru!
(lively music)
(Maki grunts)
(Miwa grunts)
Fly ball!
Nishimiya, no! Don't run yet!
[Satoru] Out!
Huh? But why?
Momo, if you don't know
the rules, then say so!
I do know them! When
the ball's hit, I run!
A sacrifice fly? What's that,
some new form of torture?
[Iori] You're just plain stupid!
[Kamo] I heard you
fought off a special-grade.
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Mostly thanks to
Todo and Gojo really.
No helmet, dude?
Itadori,
why did you want to
be a jujutsu sorcerer?
At first, it just
kinda happened,
but I'm kind of a loner so I
want to save lots of people
so that I'll have lots of them
watching over me when I die.
[Young Kamo] If
you're not there, Mom,
then I won't become
a jujutsu sorcerer!
Listen, Noritoshi,
you have talent.
You can use it to
save lots of people.
-(Young Kamo sobbing)
-The more people you save,
the more you'll be recognized.
Then in turn, all kinds
of people will help you.
You'll only be alone for now,
and one day, once you've
become a great sorcerer,
I know you'll come and get me.
Okay.
That's a good reason.
Strike!
Batter out! Change up!
[Iori] Kamo, you'll never
get a hit if you don't swing!
They call me Tanaka of Tohoku!
No, Tanaka's the
Tanaka of Tohoku.
And Tanaka's a pitcher!
[Inumaki] Bonito flakes.
(Kugisaki growls)
Huh?
What the hell is that?
Uh oh, Kugisaki
snapped! It's a free-for-all!
Hey, using a pitching
machine is against the rules!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
This is just a spare.
It's a spare Mechamaru.
We had no other choice, since
your Panda broke our main one.
Huh, a pitching machine, eh?
I guess I don't understand,
but you know a
lot about machines.
Hey, are you an otaku?
It's just one thing after
another with you, huh?
And yet somehow
you're still a student here.
(grunts) Fine! I'll
get a hit anyway!
[Itadori] All right,
she got on base!
[Fushiguro] Fueled by rage.
(casual catchy music)
[Satoru] Out!
(intense music)
(Mai scoffs)
(Maki grunts)
[Itadori] Yeah!
Gone! Home run.
Huh?
Oh!
Ah!
Ah! Cheater!
[Inumaki] Bonito flakes!
Kugisaki, go back.
Catcher, huh?
As catcher, you'll
call the shots,
lead the defense, et cetera.
One has to say it's a fitting
position for my brother,
but I want a real face-off,
a face-off with Pitcher Itadori.
Todo.
You could have
been their pitcher.
No, he couldn't.
Mechamaru had to pitch
because it's all he can do.
Promise me this, brother.
In a second, if I hit a
home run right here,
next time you'll pitch.
Ow!
(gasps) Todo! Hang in there!
Hey, nice pitch!
[Both] Nice pitch.
-Nice pitch!
-Nice pitch, Maki!
-Really, it wasn't bad.
-Way to go!
-That was a good one.
-Cool, man.
-Nice pitch, Maki.
Wow, bro.
Everyone really hates
you. I mean, everyone.
Do you still hate young Itadori?
It's not about
liking or hating him.
The fact is that Itadori
isn't allowed to exist
under jujutsu laws.
He's only still alive due
to Gojo's selfishness.
We must not bend
the rules of the group
for any one individual,
especially as we know
that many others may die
because Itadori lives.
But there are lives that
were saved thanks to him, too.
Case in point, he worked
together with Todo
to fend off the special-grade.
Not that this applies
only to our students,
but they're going to
stack up many regrets
as their lives go on.
I wish I had done that.
I wish they'd done this.
I should have said that. I
wish someone had told me this.
To be honest with you,
I don't know what
the right decision is
when it comes to Itadori.
For now, let's just
watch over him, all right?
(energetic music)
Whoa, he made it!
Yeah, Inumaki's
surprisingly fast, huh?
[Inumaki] Salted roe.
[Iori] Mai, Miwa!
Watch out for the steal!
How about we save our
regrets for another day?
(energetic music continues)
Nailed it.
Yes!
(Satoru laughing)
[Gakuganji] Yaga, do
something about Gojo first.
(closing theme music)
(singing in Japanese)
[Cast] Juju Stroll!
[Inumaki] Salmon.
I'll say rice.
But then again, I
do like bread too.
Hey, wait! Does it
come with roe on it?
I'm rice.
Rice, I suppose.
What? No way, I'm a bread girl!
[Inumaki] Salted rice ball.
Obviously it's bread
because I'm a panda!
You want me to kill you or what?
I don't know.
This one feels kind
of forced somehow.
It's not you.
They're out of ideas.
Time to go home.
(intense music)